RESUME



EDUCATION

AUGUST 1997 - JUNE 2004

Lawyer jurist

Saratov Military Institute

SEPTEMBER 2005 - SEPTEMBER 2008

Doctor of pedagogical sciences

Penza University

SKILLS

HTML / CSS /STYLED COMPONENT

JAVASCRIPT / TYPESCRIPT

NODE.JS / NEST.JS

REACT / VUE

REDUX / VUEX

WEBGL / THREE.JS

GRAPHQL / RABBITMQ

EXPRESS / MONGODB

TERRAFORM / AWS

DOCKER / LINUX

TARAS SCHEVCHENKO

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

 $\textbf{Phone: +7} (937)819-30-17, \quad | \quad \textbf{Email: shev-taras@ya.ru, } | \quad \textbf{Web: https://taras-server.ru}$

Address: 10a October Avenue, Mytishchi, Moscow, Russia, 141014,

ABOUT ME

I have 2 years experience full-stack developer. Last year I worked on a commercial project in the node.js stack, telegramm. api, nest.js, express, mongoose, webSocket, apollo, react, serviceWorker, graphQL, moment.js, rabbitmq, git, gitlab, ci/cd, google.api (development of an online store application with delivery by drivers in conjunction with a bot telegramm and nest.js backend). The project ends in March, so I'm looking for a new team.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FEBRUARY 2022 - MARCH 2023

Full-stack Developer | Moscow

Anybots, Bali, https://anybots.ru

Brief Description:

- I. development of telegram bots on node.js
- 2. website development (online store) on react.js graphQL
- 3. development of a backend for an online store on nest.js, graphQL, rabbitMQ
- 4. layout styled component
- 5. web push notifications
- 6. ci/cd and deploy to docker
- 7. mongoDB development and database administration
- 8. customer support chat in English

OCTOBER 2022 - DECEMBER 2022 & DECEMBER 2021 - FEBRUARY 2022

Full-stack Developer | Moscow

Mgl-parts, Moscow, https://mgl-parts.com

Brief Description:

- I. Development of a telegram bot for systematizing the inventory of auto parts on node is
- 2. Participation in the discussion of the technology stack of the concept, development of terms of reference
- 3. MongoDB development and database administration
- 5. Deploying project infrastructure on ubuntu server, support
- 6. Development of sales scripts in JavaScript